♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪When you say you love me♪
♪It's more than I ever imagined♪
♪Slowly♪
♪Stay by my side♪
♪Love is the warmth of everyday life♪
♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪You lean your forehead against mine♪
♪Then you keep grinning like a fool♪
♪Little by little♪
♪You come closer to me♪
♪A warm love song plays in my ear♪
=The One=
=Episode 13=
Learn how to kiss yet?
I'll teach you.
No.
Why won't you let me kiss you?
Not even in a dream?
Why do you want to kiss me?
Because...
I like you.
You like me?
W-would just any guy do?
Do you know me?
Do you know who I am?
Aren't you Cheng Lin?
You like Cheng Lin?
Mm.
Then why did you...
My mom...
What did my mom say to you?
What did she say to you?
♪I replay it all again in my mind♪
♪Is it hard to forget what I never had?♪
♪Can you hear how much I miss you?♪
♪It hits like a wave I can't contain♪
Why won't you let me kiss you?
Is it because I'm older?
Or because you think I'm...
dirty?
Tell me.
What is Cheng Lin to you?
(My head hurts. Everything hurts.)
(Why am I so tired?)
Morning.
Tired?
(Did time rewind?)
Sit down.
(Why is he...)
(Why wouldn't you let me kiss you?)
Drink some water first.
I was drunk last night.
That was my fault.
After breakfast,
you should head home.
(Cheng Lin is mine. - Su Yan)
(Cheng Lin is mine.)
(I want to kiss him.)
(And sleep with him.)
Delete that. That's private.
Then sue me.
I'll face the consequences.
You...
(Master of the law,
yet a master of seduction.)
(All skill, no morals.)
(Campus seductress. Homewrecker.)
(Su Yan.)
(Tell me.)
(What would make you feel better?)
♪Can you hear how much I miss you?♪
♪It hits like a wave I can't contain♪
♪I can't let go of the path we shared♪
♪But you said time would make it fade♪
♪Memories pile up, moment by moment♪
♪One careless word brings my walls down♪
♪I escape the past, then fall back in♪
♪Longing twists into a hopeless knot♪
♪Pulled by the past
till my world fades out♪
♪I hum this song alone♪
♪Counting every fleeting moment♪
♪Every corner still reminds me of you♪
♪Can you hear how much I miss you?♪
♪It hits like a wave I can't contain♪
♪I can't let go of the path we shared♪
♪But you said time would make it fade♪